I don't know everything. I know some of y'all think I think I know everything because I speak
with conviction, because I have no interest in listening to people who try to counter me without
facts, because ultimately I don't speak on much that I don't know about. Nonetheless, I am very
open and willing to hear other people's perspectives, particularly about things that don't directly
affect me because they have a firsthand experience that I don't have. That said, the inability
to bring new perspectives, new insights into the conversation without couching them in insults
is something I will continuously address because it stands in the way of our ability to expand
intellectually. You see, there's always people who will want to share something new with me or
share a differing perspective with me that so that feel inclined to do so by starting
with, I expect you to, or I'm disappointed that you don't, or, you know, someone like you
should know better. No, no, that is not useful. It is also literally counterintuitive and
counterproductive to your purpose of even addressing me because nothing about what you're saying
requires you to undermine my character or my intellect. Instead of bringing me in, you're
pushing me out. And when you push me out, baby, once you started, I'm already gone and my fingers
already coming right here to block your ass. How black am I going to have to get? How black,
I love it.